export const Quizdata = [
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not an OOP?",
        options: ["C", "C++", "Python", "javascript"],
        answer: 1,
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used in web-Development?",
        options: ["C", "C++", "Python", "javascript"],
        answer: 4,
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: "What is an example of iteration in C?",
        options: ["For", "While", "Do-While", "All"],
        answer: 4,
        level: "Hard"
    },
    {
        question: "The C-preprocessors are specified with _________ symbol.",
        options: ["#", "$", "&", "*"],
        answer: 1,
        level: "Hard"
    },
    {
        question: "What is #include <stdio.h>?",
        options: ["Preprocessor directive", "Inclusion directive", "File inclusion directive", "None of the mentioned"],
        answer: 1,
        level: "Hard"
    },
    {
        question: "In C language, FILE is of which data type?",
        options: ["Int", "Char*", "Struct", "None"],
        answer: 3,
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used in web-Development?",
        options: ["C", "C++", "Python", "javascript"],
        answer: 4,
        level: "Hard"
    },
    {
        question: "Which keyword is used to prevent any changes in the variable within a C program?",
        options: ["Immutable", "mutable", "Const", "Volatile"],
        answer: 3,
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not used in web-Development?",
        options: ["C", "CSS", "HTML", "javascript"],
        answer: 1,
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the father of C language?",
        options: ["Steve Jobs", "James Gosling", "Dennis Ritchie", "Rasmus Lerdorf"],
        answer: 3,
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not a valid C variable name?",
        options: ["int number;", "float rate;", "int variable_count;", "int $main;"],
        answer: 4,
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following cannot be a variable name in C?",
        options: ["volatile", "true", "Friend", "User"],
        answer: 2,
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is Easy to learn?",
        options: ["C", "C++", "Python", "javascript"],
        answer: 3,
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is difficult to learn?",
        options: ["C++", "C", "Python", "javascript"],
        answer: 1,
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: "Functions can return enumeration constants in C?",
        options: ["true", "false", "Depends", "Standard Dependency"],
        answer: 1,
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: "C preprocessors can have compiler specific features.",
        options: ["True", "False", "Can't Say", "May Be"],
        answer: 1,
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: "Who developed Python Programming Language?",
        options: ["Wick van Rossum", "Rasmus Lerdorf", "Guido van Rossum", "Niene Stom"],
        answer: 3,
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the size of float and double in java?",
        options: ["32 64", "32 32", "64 32", "64 64"],
        answer: 1,
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: "Number of primitive data types in Java are?",
        options: ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
        answer: 3,
        level: "Hard"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following typecasting is accepted by C language?",
        options: ["Widening conversions", "Narrowing conversions", "Widening & Narrowing conversions", "None of the mentioned"],
        answer: 3,
        level: "Medium"
    },

];